Toni Morrison Papers, 1917-2015: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1917-2015; 66 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Novels, 1917-2015; 1970-2015; 66 boxes
    - Paradise, 1971-2014; 1992-2014; 11 boxes
      - Grace, 1994 August 18-September 6; 1 folder
        - "'What will you do now?'", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
          Pages 90-93.
        - Chapter 3: Grace, July 2 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
          Pages 79-122.
      - Seneca, circa 1994-1997; 3 folders
        - Seneca, 1994 September 10; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Seneca, 1994 September 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - "Relieved to learn...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected (photocopy). 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
          Pages 2-16.
        - Seneca, 1994 September 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Seneca, 1994 December 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
          Pages 4-29.
        - Seneca, 1995 May 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
          Pages 94-132.
        - Seneca, 1995 June 2; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 94-136.
        - "Dovey, at the town's treatment of her father...", circa 1994-1997; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 145-151.
        - "up and moved, towns intoxicated with wealth...", circa 1994-1997; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 159-160.
        - "letting Sand wait...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 163-178.
        - "would melt in his mouth...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 166-176.
        - "my house...", circa 1994-1997; Printout (photocopy), corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 192-204.
        - Chapter 4: Seneca, June 30 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
          Pages 123-218 (red pencil 222).
        - Chapter 4: Seneca, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 6)
          Pages 123-207.
      - Divine, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders
        - Chapter 5: Divine, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
          Pages 203-214.
        - "'Let me tell you about love...'", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
          Pages 206-223.
        - Chapter 5: Divine, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
          Pages 205-229.
        - "of their eternal lives...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
          Pages 208-229.
        - Chapter 5: Divine, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
          Pages 205-267.
        - Chapter 5: Divine, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
          Pages 205-238.
        - Chapter 5: Divine, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
          Pages 208-213.
        - "ever I see one...", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
          Page 268.
        - "'Cut it out, Gigi!'", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
          Pages 272-277.
        - Chapter 5: Divine, July 2 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
          Pages 208-279 (pencil 219-290; red pencil 223).
      - Patricia, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders
        - Patricia, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 280-297.
        - Patricia, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 280-298.
        - Patricia, September 8 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 280-294; with "Pat's notes," numbered pp.13-16.
        - Patricia, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 280-299.
        - "Bells and pine trees...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 281-307.
        - Chapter 6: Patricia, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
          Pages 280-310 (pencil 291-321).
        - Chapter 6: Patricia, June 11 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
          Pages 291-334.
        - "I be there, Miss Best.", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
          Pages 342-343.
        - Chapter 6: Patricia, July 1 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
          Pages 291-346.
        - Chapter 6: Patricia, July 1 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
          Pages 291-348 (pen 297-354).
      - Consolata, circa 1994-1997; 3 folders
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-[331].
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-[337].
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-328.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-338.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-354.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, April 29 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322-357.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, June 20 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
          Pages 322 (pen 347)-359.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, June 25 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
          Pages 347-397.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, July 11 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
          Pages 347 (pencil 349)-401.
        - "looking so hard...", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
          Pages 398-417.
        - "couldn't have seen it anyway.", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
          Pages 409-425.
        - "care; required no emotional investment...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
          Pages 427-431.
        - Chapter 7: Consolata, August 11 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 35, Folder 7)
          Pages 349 (pencil 354, 355)-433.
      - Lone, circa 1994-1997; 1 folder
        - "Only women walk this road...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Chapter 8: Lone, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Chapter 8: Lone, July 30 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Chapter 8: Lone, August 3 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 434-454.
        - Chapter 8: Lone, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 434-457.
        - Chapter 8: Lone, August 8 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 436-462.
        - "DuPres and nephew", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 463-467.
        - "current generation...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 464-468.
        - "DuPres and nephew...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 463-468.
        - "None of the current DuPres...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Pages 464-472.
        - "that the women...", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 1)
          Page 498.
      - Save-Marie, circa 1994-1997; 1 folder
        - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 21 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - "their selfishness had trashed...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 21 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
          Pages 480-487.
        - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 23 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
          Pages 480-496.
        - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 26 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
          Pages 480-498.
        - Chapter 9: Save-Marie, August 28 no year; Printout. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
          Pages 480-512.
      - "In ocean hush...", circa 1994-1997; 1 folder
        - "In ocean hush...", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - "In ocean hush...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 3)
          1 pp.
      - Paradise Drafts, 1995 January 3-1997; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Paradise Draft, 1995 January 3; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Paradise Draft, 1995 April 23; Printout. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-124.
        - Paradise Draft, 1995 June 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-165.
        - Paradise Draft, 1995 August 10; Printout. 1 item (Box 36, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-171.
        - Paradise Draft, 1996 June 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 37, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-202.
        - Paradise Draft, circa 1996-1997; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 37, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-203.
        - Paradise Draft, 1997 July 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 37, Folder 3-6)
        - Paradise Draft, circa 1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
          Pages 1-534.
      - Paradise Setting Copy, 1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 38, Folder 4-6)
      - Paradise First Pass Rough Pages Duplicate, 1997 October 20; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
        Pages a-b, i-viii, 1-304. With cover page from Jill Lynch and 2 notepad pages of corrections.
      - Paradise First Pass Master Set, 1997 October 21; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
        Pages a-b, i-viii, 1-326. With publisher memo dated November 3, 1997.
      - Paradise Second Pass Proofs Author Set, 1997 November 3; 1 item (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
        Pages i-viii, 1-325.
      - Paradise Second Pass Proofs Master Set, 1997 November 3; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 1)
        Pages b, iii-iv, 5-324. With publisher memo, dated November 11, 1997.
      - Paradise Third Pass Proofs, 1997 November 11; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
        Pages b, i-viii,1-326.
      - Paradise Blueline Proofs with Corrected Pages, 1997; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 4)
        Pages [1]-318, revised laser pages 293-319, and Knopf correspondence dated November 19,1997.
      - Paradise Advance Copy, 1998; 1 item (Box 40, Folder 5)
        Pages [1]-321.
      - Paradise Foreword, 2005; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Paradise Introduction, circa 2014; Notepad pages, corrected printout and photocopy. 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Love, 1999 January 28-2003; 7 boxes
      Working titles Sporting Woman (abbreviated Sp. W)and L. Note that chapter drafts are grouped according to their name and order in the published book, although, as their individual titles reflect, they were renamed and reordered throughout the writing process.
      - Outlines and Notes, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
        Printouts and handwritten notes and organizational outlines; Robert Gottlieb's comments.
      - "The settlement is a planet away from Cosey's Resort...", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - "Do you like my Boyfriend?", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - "helpmate. Content to serve.", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - "L.3. The Ocean is my man now.", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - "Chapter Six (Bachelor)", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - "Chap. 3 The sad little orange trees...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - "She didn't need to know...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - "Notes: material tk", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - "The boots, probably, which she never took off...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - "Families make the best enemies...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - "So he planned an outing with Romen.", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - "afraid L's threat...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - "The bottled cotton-mouth...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - "Burrowing under blankets...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - "i.e. so hot...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - "Sketch for Chap. Nine 'Father'", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - "Jailhouse", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - "Last chap.", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - "A Sporting Woman", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - "Chapter 1 [N.B. Lost his coat--came home late on community bus with Vida]", undated; Notepad pages. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - "Chapter 4", undated; Notepad pages. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Notes and Early Drafts, 1999 January 28-2000 December 2; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, undated; 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "1. which line is secondary (enslavement)", undated; Notepad pages. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Notes, 1999 January 28; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Organization, undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "She came in there and solved all their problems...", undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 2-6.
        - "She came in there and solved all their problems...", June 5 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 2-8.
        - "Her wee hands...", July 22 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "Her wee hands...", August 4 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "Her wee hands...", August 11 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "We need a better story...", August 16 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "We need a better story...", undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Storyvoice, undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - "Sandler Gibbons was wiping salt dust...", undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Sp. W, 2000 February; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Sp. W, 2000 February 8; Printout. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Sp. W, 2000 February 12; Printout. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 28-32.
        - Sp. W, 2000 February 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Sp. W, 2000 May 15; 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - Sp. W, 2000 May 16; Printout. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 8-16.
        - Sp. W, 2000 May 16; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 36-40.
        - Sp. W, 2000 November 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 1-2, 1-11.
        - Sp. W, 2000 December 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 41, Folder 24)
          Pages 43-47.
      - Miscellaneous Chapter Drafts, 2000 August 3-2001 May 10; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, undated; 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Chapter 1, 2000 August 3; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
          Page 12, 10-35.
        - Chapter 1, 2001 April 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-45.
        - Chapter 3, undated; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - L, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Sporting Woman: Story Voice, 2000 July 28; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Sp. W, 2000 December 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Sp. W: L, 2001 April 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - SW Chapter 1 (including L1), December 16 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - L, 2002 May 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - L, 2002 October 1; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - "The women's legs are spread wide open...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 1: Portrait, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Sp. W: L's voice and Chapter 1, 2000 July 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Sp. W: Story Voice and Chapter 1, 2000 July 10; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Sp. W: Chapter 1, 2000 December 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Pages 14-43.
        - Sp. W: Chapter 1, 2001 April 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Pages 15-43.
        - Chapter 1: Image, 2002 July 3; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Pages 15-45.
        - "tomorrow?", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Page 45 and inserts.
        - S.W.: L and Chapter 1, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-47.
        - S.W.: Chapter 1, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 3)
          Pages 15-47.
      - Chapter 2: Friend, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - SW Chapter 2, 2000 December 29; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - "That flooded his chest", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - SW Chapter 2, 2001 January 2; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - SW Chapter 2, 2001 January 2; 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - SW Chapter 2, 2001 January 5; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - SW Chapter 2, 2001 January 19; tktktk 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
          Pages tk-tk.
        - SW Chapter 2, 2001 April 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - "Vida was all he knew...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
          1 p. (page 22 of 30).
        - Chapter 2, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 2, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - "Vida set up the ironing board...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 3: Stranger, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Filed as Junior Vivian, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 4 [formerly under Junior Vivian], 2001 January 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 4: Enemy/Predator?, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 3: Stranger, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - "District 10", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 5)
          Pages 6, 15, 22.
      - L2, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1999-2003; 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Sp. W: L, 2000 July 28; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
          Pages 36-41.
        - Sp. W: L, 2000 December 2; Printout, corrected. Pages 41-47. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Sp. W: L, 2000 December 14; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
          Page 43.
        - Sp. W: L:b, 2001 January 1; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
          Pages 44-49.
        - L: b, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
          Pages 47-52.
        - L2, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, December 22 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, 2002 June 27; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, 2002 August 14; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - L2, 2002 August 14; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 4: Benefactor, circa 1999-2003; 2 folders
        - SW Chapter 5, 2001 July 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 6, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 June 3; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 5/Now Chapter 4, June 6 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 4: Benefactor, 2002 June 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - "Heed eased down...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - "Heed was sure...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - SW Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - SW Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
          Pages 8-9.
        - SW Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - SW Chapter 3, 2001 May 10; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Chapter 3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - End of Chapter 4, 2002 June 3; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - "An orange-scented road...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - L3, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - L ff Chap. 7, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L To follow Chapter 7, 2001 February 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L, 2001 July 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L3, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L3, 2002 August 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - L3, 2002 August 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Corrections pp. 1-8 reprinted, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - "The Ocean is my man now...", circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 5: Lover, circa 1999-2003; 1 folder
        - Chapter 5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1999-2003; Printout. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 6: Bachelor, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5: Lover, circa 1999-2003; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5, 2002 June 27; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 July 9; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Chapter 5: Lover, 2002 July 9; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 43, Folder 2)